timesofap.com 2014-03-22

# Andhra Pradesh, Telangana, Seemandhra, Rayalaseema AP News Latest Updates Live Breaking News - Timesofap.com

Timesofap.com respects the privacy of it’s users and is committed to protect it in all respects. With a view to offer most enriching and holistic internet experience to it’s users. timesofap.com offers a vast repository of Online Sites and variety of community services. Most of the Online Community Services are offered for free but you need a Universal mandatory registration to surf timesofap.com sites in detail. The information about the user as collected by timesofap.com is: (1) information supplied by users and (2) information automatically tracked while navigation.

**We want you to:**

a. feel comfortable using our web sites  
b. feel secure submitting information to us  
c. contact us with your questions or concerns about privacy on this site  
d. know that by using our sites you are consenting to the collection of certain data

We may collect certain anonymous information in standard usage logs through our Web server, including computer-identification information obtained from "cookies", sent to your browser from a

1\. web server and stored on your hard drive  
2\. an IP address, assigned to the computer which you use  
3\. the domain server through which you access our service  
4\. the type of computer you're using  
5\. the type of web browser you're using

**We may collect the following personally identifiable information about you:**

1\. name  
2\. email address  
3\. ZIP/Postal code  
4\. demographic profile (like your age, gender,occupation,education and durables owned)  
5\. interests (such as news, sports, travel and so on)  
6\. financial information (like account or credit card numbers)  
7\. opinions of features on our website(s).

**Who Geathers the Information?**

1\. We will collect anonymous traffic information from you when you visit our site.  
2\. We will collect personally identifiable information about you only as part of a voluntary registration process, on-line survey or contest.  
3\. Our advertisers may collect anonymous traffic information from their own assigned cookies to your browser.  
4\. The Site contains links to other Web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such Web sites.  
5\. We may make chat rooms, forums, instant messenger and message boards and other services available to you. Please understand that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. We have no control over its use and you should exercise caution when disclosing your personal information to anyone.

**How's the Information using?**

We use personal information to:

1\. help us provide personalized features  
2\. tailor our sites to your interest  
3\. get in touch with you when necessary

**We use contact information internally to:**

1\. direct our efforts for product improvement  
2\. contact you as a survey respondent  
3\. notify you if you win any contest  
4\. send you promotional materials from our contest sponsors or advertisers

**Generally, we use anonymous traffic information to:**

1\. remind us of who you are in order to deliver to you a better and more personalized service from both an advertising and an editorial perspective  
2\. recognize your access privileges to our Web sites  
3\. track your entries in some of our promotions, sweepstakes and contests to indicate a player's progress through the promotion and to track entries, submissions, and status in prize drawings  
4\. make sure that you don't see the same ad repeatedly  
5\. help diagnose problems with our server  
6\. administer our Web sites  
7\. track your session so that we can understand better how people use our sites

Our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer’s connection to the Internet, including your IP address, when you visit our site. (Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send you data — such as the web pages you view.) Your IP address does not identify you personally. We use this information to deliver our web pages to you upon request, to tailor our site to the interests of our users, to measure traffic within our site and let advertisers know the geographic locations from where our visitors come.

All information gathered on timesofap.com is securely stored within the timesofap.com controlled database. The database is stored on servers secured behind a firewall; access to the servers is password-protected and is strictly limited. However, as effective as our security measures are, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. And, of course, any information you include in a posting to the discussion areas is available to anyone with Internet access.

We don't sell, transfer any personal or business data we collected. We do our best to keep our site safe. But since all data are inputed by users or automated, sometime we don't have enough time/control to monitor all the data collected. So we strongly suggest parents' supervise when a child visit our site. If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please write to us admin@timesofap.com
